<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sprout</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="recom">Recommendation</string>
    <string name="your_record">Your record</string>
    <string name="plant_name">Name:</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview:</string>
    <string name="alias">Alias:</string>
    <string name="channel_name">channel_name</string>
    <string name="channel_description">channel_description</string>
    <string name="read">This is an Android-based platform application tailor-made for families with children who is able to easily query and read common plant knowledge outside of school time as well as to provide a set of entertaining planting plans to cultivate children with hands-on ability, increase the interest in acquiring knowledge, and even improve the closeness of the parent-child relationship.</string>
    <string name="read1">The target audience for this app are families with children. The expected range of age is at 12 to 15, because children of this age group are in the enlightenment stage where they begin to acquire external knowledge and become interested, but they often cannot complete a long-term job independently. Therefore, stimulating the curiosity of children of this age is the main focus and motivation of the app.</string>
    <string name="slogan">Unwilling to lonely and mediocre, the pursuit of struggle and glory.</string>
    <string name="searching">Find a plant by inputting any information of the plant, such as name, water need, harvest cycle. Then the detailed information is provided.</string>
    <string name="recognition">Recognize the plant by taking or uploading the pictures.</string>
    <string name="planning">Make your own planting plan, we will help you to record the whole process, and remind you to water on time.</string>
    <string name="medal_ins">According to your planting check-in record, when reaching a certain number, you will get the corresponding medal reward.</string>
    <string name="insectionSign">1. Leaves with brown spots, holes, nibbled edges</string>
    <string name="infectionSolution">1. Isolate the plant.</string>
    <string name="overWaterSign">1. Withered, drooping or black leaves</string>
    <string name="overWaterSolution">1. Water the plants usually but less often</string>
    <string name="dehy">1. "Crispy" leaves.</string>
    <string name="deh_solution">1. Increase the frequency of watering</string>
    <string name="nutrition_sign">1. Yellowing tip and margin</string>
    <string name="nutrition_solution">1. Add compost to the soil</string>
    <string name="sunlight_sign">1. Leaves with lanky, floppy, pale</string>
    <string name="sunlight_solution">1. Move the plants to the windowsill</string>
    <string name="sick_title">What happened to your plants?</string>
    <string-array name="virtual_plan_days">
        <item>3</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>7</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
