<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sprout</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="recom">Recommendation</string>
    <string name="your_record">Your record</string>
    <string name="plant_name">Name:</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview:</string>
    <string name="alias">Alias:</string>
    <string name="channel_name">channel_name</string>
    <string name="channel_description">channel_description</string>
    <string name="read">This is an Android-based platform application tailor-made for families with children who is able to easily query and read common plant knowledge outside of school time as well as to provide a set of entertaining planting plans to cultivate children with hands-on ability, increase the interest in acquiring knowledge, and even improve the closeness of the parent-child relationship.</string>
    <string name="read1">The target audience for this app are families with children. The expected range of age is at 12 to 15, because children of this age group are in the enlightenment stage where they begin to acquire external knowledge and become interested, but they often cannot complete a long-term job independently. Therefore, stimulating the curiosity of children of this age is the main focus and motivation of the app.</string>
    <string name="slogan">Unwilling to lonely and mediocre, the pursuit of struggle and glory.</string>
    <string name="searching">Find a plant by inputting any information of the plant, such as name, water need, harvest cycle. Then the detailed information is provided.</string>
    <string name="recognition">Recognize the plant by taking or uploading the pictures.</string>
    <string name="planning">Make your own planting plan, we will help you to record the whole process, and remind you to water on time.</string>
    <string name="medal_ins">According to your planting check-in record, when reaching a certain number, you will get the corresponding medal reward.</string>
    <string name="insectionSign">Leaves with brown spots, holes, nibbled edges or insects anywhere on the plant.</string>
    <string name="infectionSolution">Isolate the plant, remove all infected leaves, and then wipe off the insects with a damp cloth or soapy water. Application neem oil helps control pests and fungi in many houseplants because it is also an organic insecticide.</string>
    <string name="overWaterSign">Withered, drooping or black leaves, die leaves remain soft and pliable.</string>
    <string name="overWaterSolution">Water the plants usually but less often, so that the water soaks the soil thoroughly. This will encourage stronger root growth as the plant learns that it is not watering hard enough and therefore needs to store the water it does get.</string>
    <string name="dehy">"Crispy" leaves, leaves with brown leaf tips or edges, water passes through the soil without soaking in</string>
    <string name="deh_solution">Increase the frequency of watering, and on your first watering, make sure to dip a handful of water or a basin into the sink thoroughly, then run the faucet in a trickle for 15 minutes. Another solution is to reassemble the plant in a larger container, as the roots may be tightly tied together and compete for space (and water).</string>
    <string name="nutrition_sign">Yellowing tip and margin, yellowing leaf</string>
    <string name="nutrition_solution">Adding organic materials to the soil (such as compost or coffee grounds) also reduces pH slowly over time, extending microbial life and improving soil structure. In particular, plants with low iron content require soils with a pH below 7, which can be promoted by adding acidic mulch (such as pine needles).</string>
    <string name="sunlight_sign">Leaves with lanky, floppy, pale</string>
    <string name="sunlight_solution">Some plants need direct sunlight, while others only need indirect sunlight. Figuring out the type of plant that works best for you will help you determine if you\'re getting enough. Move the plants to the windowsill, keeping the blinds open and moving the plants as little as possible, as they usually have to reorient themselves to the sun by growing new leaves.</string>
    <string name="sick_title">What happened to your plants?</string>
    <string-array name="virtual_plan_days">
        <item>3</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>7</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
